stattrek.com 2011-05-29

# Stat Trek Privacy Policy

Here is the bottom line. Your privacy is very important to us. We do not sell or rent your personal information to anyone. 

### Privacy Policy Overview

In general, you can browse the Stat Trek site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. 

If you choose to use certain services, we may ask you to provide contact information, identity information, and/or billing information. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature. 

### How We Use Your Information

We use the personal information that you provide for three basic purposes. 

  * To respond to email queries. 
  * To send the Stat Trek newsletter to subscribers. 
  * To process payment for fee-based services.

To maximize security and protect Users, financial transactions are handled over a secure connection by PayPal Bank. Stat Trek neither sees nor retains User financial information. 

We offer you the ability to review and change the information you submit to us. Licensed users can change their User ID, password, email address, contact information, security information, and User preferences on the My Profile page. Subscribers to the Stat Trek newsletter can "unsubscribe" and purge their email address from our subscriber list at the Newsletter page. 

### Third-Party Advertisers

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to  contact us.
